Finding Aid for the Ray Bolger Papers LSC.1117
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 4. Stage Projects, ca. 1930s-1980s; Boxes 2, 13-16, 27, 29, 33-38, 41, 43-44, 48, 50, 53, 74, 76-78, 102-104, 107-108,114-115
  - Capitol Theater - program, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Charley's Aunt - album recording, no date (Box 115)
  - Come Summer - clippings, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Come Summer - contract, 1968 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Come Summer - fan mail and well wishes, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Come Summer - letters to Bolger, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Come Summer - letters to Bolger, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Come Summer - playbills, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Come Summer - production list and communications from Seldon, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Come Summer - script, 1969, no date (Box 13, Folder 9)
    With playbill.
  - Come Summer - script, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Come Summer - script pages, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Come Summer - script pages, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Come Summer - script pages, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Come Summer - script pages and music, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Come Summer - scripts, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Come Summer - telegrams, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Die Fledermaus - script, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    With correspondence.
  - Empire Room, Waldorf Astoria - ephemera, no date, 1960, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Empire Room, Waldorf Astoria - publicity and clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    With Walter Winchell press release.
  - Fol de Rol - programs, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Fol de Rol - programs, no date, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - George White's Scandals - clippings, 1930-1932 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - George White's Scandals - lyrics, no date (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Happy Time (The) - clippings, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Happy Time (The) - contracts, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    With some box office sales statements.
  - Happy Time (The) - script and programs, 1969, no date (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Keep of the Grass - photographs, no date (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Life Begins at 8:40 - photographs, no date (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Life Begins at 8:40 - playbills, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Life Begins at 8:40 - scene pages, no date (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Window Dresser Goes to Bed, New Deal Ladies Circle, Let's Take a Walk Around the Block, C'est La Vie, and Rabelais, Balzac, de Maupassant, Boccaccio.
  - On Your Toes - clippings and ephemera, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - On Your Toes - photographs, no date (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - On Your Toes - script and publicity, 1936, no date (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Palmer House, Chicago - clippings, 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Palmer House, Chicago - clippings and ephemera, 1963, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    With photograph.
  - Palmer House, Chicago - contracts, 1964-1965, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Ray Bolger's World - contracts, ca. 1970s (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Ray Bolger's World - correspondence and ephemera, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Sahara - clippings, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Sahara - programs and ephemera, 1955, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Sahara - publicity stills and photographs, no date, 1956 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Sahara - script material, no date (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Sketch of Bolger from Where's Charley by Gregory d'Alessio, 1949 (Box 125, Folder 23)
  - Think Mink - photographs, 1958 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Think Mink - telegrams, ephemera, and photographs, 1958, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Three to Make Ready - clippings, no date, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Three to Make Ready - sketches and ephemera, no date (Box 15, Folder 4)
    With Shoe on the Other Foot dated February 10, 1955.
  - Van Wezel Concert - ephemera and clippings, 1977, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Vanities - clippings, 1934 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Vanities - playbills, no date, 1933-1934 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Venetian Room, Fairmont Hotel - clippings, publicity, and ephemera, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Where's Charley - open reel, no date (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Where's Charley? - clippings and ephemera, 1949-1951 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Where's Charley? - playbills and ephemera, 1948-1952 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Where's Charley? - publicity stills, no date (Box 107, Folder 5)
    Appears to be for stage production of Where's Charley. See also Motion Picture Projects.
  - Where's Charley? - publicity stills, no date (Box 108, Folder 1)
    Appears to be related to Where's Charley stage production. Includes a miniature accordion-type book of images. See also Motion Picture Projects.
  - Where's Charley? - statements of operation and production costs, 1948-1950 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Where's Charley? - stills, playbill and lyrics, 1949, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    With script material and synopses for Charley's Aunt.
  - Where's Charley? - telegrams, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Where's Charley?- letters to Bolger, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Series 5. Radio Projects, no dates, 1944-1945, 1949; Boxes 9-10, 104
  The Radio Projects series contains a small amount of scripts, photographs and correspondence. The material in this series appears to be mostly from the 1940s. The series is arranged alphabetically by project.
  - American Theatre Wing Stage Door Canteen -script, 1944 Nov 17 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Appears to include Fox Hole Sketch.
  - Audition script for Ray Bolger, no date (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Donaldson Awards - script, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Philco Radio Hall of Fame - script, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    For segment: The Two Mrs. Carrolls
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - photographs and script material, 1945 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    Appears to be for the Ray Bolger radio show.
  - Ray Bolger's Dancing School - script, no date (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Series 6. Audio Recording and Short Film Projects, no dates, 1963, ca. late 1970s early 1980s; Boxes 16, 36, 50-51, 80, 83, 103, 132, 137, 138
  The Audio Recording and Short Film Projects series consists mainly of scripts, ephemera, stills, and publicity for Lil Elfy. Additionally there is a small amount of scripts, correspondence, publicity, and clippings for other audio recording projects including the Shire Films short film titled Peter and the Wolf. (Additional Shire Film projects are found in the Unidentified Projects series.) The series is arranged alphabetically by project.
  - Churkendoose - commercially released 45 rpm disc, 1951 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Churkendoose (The) - commercially released 45 rpm disc (2 copies), no date (Box 83)
  - I'll Elfy - commercially released 45 rpm disc (3 copies), no date (Box 83)
  - Land of Oz (The) - audio book script material, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Bolger regarding Churkendoose tape, no date, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Lil' Elfy - 33 1/3 discs (3 discs), no date (Box 138)
  - Lil' Elfy - commercially released 45 rpm disc, no date (Box 138)
  - Lil' Elfy - commercially released 45 rpm discs, no date (Box 127, Folder 2)
    6 items.
  - Lil' Elfy - ephemera, stills and publicity, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Posters removed to Box 43, Folder 2.
  - Lil' Elfy - ephemera, stills, and publicity, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    See Box 16, Folder 8.
  - Lil' Elfy - photographs, no date, 1964 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Lil' Elfy - sheet music pages, no date (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Peter and the Wolf clippings, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Peter and the Wolf scripts and correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Produced by Shire Films.
  - Wizard of Oz (The) - audio book recording script and royalties statement, 1975, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Wizard of Oz (The) and Queen Zixi of IX audio book recording discs (2 discs), 1976-1977 (Box 137)
- Series 7. Sound Recordings, 1945, 1949-1951, 1953, 1957, 1963; Boxes 1945, 1949-1951, 1953, 1957, 1963; Boxes 81-83, 86, 114-116, 136- 138
  The Sound Recordings series consists of transcription discs and commercial recordings for various projects, appearances and events. Among the projects represented are The Donaldson Awards, The Ray Bolger Show, The Red Skelton Hour, Wheres Charley, as well as a small number of unidentified items. The series is arranged alphabetically by recording title. Audio materials in this series are restricted and require advance notice for use.
  - Albums, no date (Box 115)
    Including Butterly, What Even Happened to Ol' Jack, The Wizard of Oz, and Nola Penthouse Sound Studios
  - Assorted open reels, no date (Box 114)
    Includes Ray Bolger Christmas Show, Telephone Hour, The American Showmen, Gwen Bolger interview, Ray Bolger with John Campbell, and other assorted open reels.
  - Assorted open reels, no date, 1963 (Box 115)
    Includes Voice of America: The American Musical Theater #17,
  - Audio cassette tapes and one open reel, no date (Box 116)
  - Audio Recordings, no date (Box 85)
    12 5-inch reel-to-reel tapes; 19 7-inch reel-to-reel tapes; 6 audio cassette tapes.
  - Bolger spot - 7" reel, no date (Box 127)
  - Castles in Spain - 78 rpm disc, 1961 (Box 137)
    May be related to Babes in Toyland.
  - Catholic Charities 31st Annual Appeal "On Stage" - 4 transcription discs, 1950 April 27 (Box 82)
  - Come Summer demonstration 33 1/3 discs and sheet music (4 discs), 1969 (Box 137)
  - Commercially released LPs by other performers - 10 discs, no date (Box 86)
  - Demo recordings - 7" reel, 1958 (Box 138)
  - Donaldson Awards - 6 transcription discs, 1949 July 12 (Box 86)
    Found in box annotated Donaldson Awards Tex and Jinx Records.
  - Ethel Merman and Ray Bolger - commercially released 78 rpm disc, no date (Box 83)
  - Ethel Merman and Ray Bolger - commercially released record discs (3 discs), no date (Box 138)
    Featuring Bolger and Ethel Merman. Dearie and I Said My Pajamas (And Put On My Pray'rs).
  - Good Old Fashioned Balls/A Song About Peanuts - 45 rpm disc, no date (Box 83)
  - Governor Reagan First 90 Days - 5" reel, no date (Box 127)
  - Hi-Jinx Show (The) - 3 transcription discs, 1949 May 23 (Box 81)
  - Hi-Jinx Show (The) - 3 transcription discs, 1949 July 27 (Box 81)
  - Max Mainspring the Mechanical Man - commercially released 78 rpm disc, c. 1950 (Box 83)
  - Max Mainspring the Mechanical Man - commercially released 78 rpm disc, no date (Box 138)
  - Melody Cruise to Havana - record disc, no date (Box 138)
  - My Fair Lady - 33 1/2 LP, 1978 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - NBC transcription discs (2 discs), no date (Box 137)
    Amy, Builderupper, Cherries, Slaughter,Wizard.
  - Ray Bolger - 7" reel, 1964 (Box 127)
  - Ray Bolger compilation album, 1953 (Box 127)
  - Ray Bolger interview with Radio Free Europe, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    With typed transcript.
  - Ray Bolger Reel #1 - 7" reel, no date (Box 127)
  - Ray Bolger Show (The) - 14 transcription discs, 1945 (Box 81)
  - Ray Bolger Show songs, 1953 (Box 115)
  - Skelton Hour transcription disc, no date (Box 83)
  - Unidentified projects - 13 transcription discs, no date (Box 82)
  - Unidentified projects - 2 transcription discs, 1949 May 8 (Box 82)
  - Unidentified projects - 5 transcription discs, no date (Box 83)
  - US Committee for UNICEF and United Nation Radio Special Halloween Show - disc, 1957 (Box 115)
    Includes The Trail of Sargent Bill and Trick or Treat for UNICEF
  - Various commercially released 45 and 33 1/3 rpm and discs by other performers, no date (Box 138)
    Bolger does not appear to have performed in any of the record albums.
  - Various commercially released 78 rpm discs by other performers (30 discs), no date (Box 84)
  - Various commercially released 78 rpm discs by other performers (39 discs) (Box 136)
  - We Care - 2 transcription discs, 1949 Nov 22 (Box 82)
  - Western Airlines - 33 1/2 LP, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Where's Charley - 6 transcription discs, 1951 (Box 81)
- Series 8. Armed Services Entertainment, no dates, ca. early 1940s; Boxes 33, 36, 105
  The Armed Services Entertainment series is script material, correspondence, ephemera, and photographs relating to Bolgers involvement with the USO during World War II. There is no specific arrangement to the series.
  - Script material, correspondence, papers and ephemera, 1941-1944, 1956 (Box 33)
  - U.S.O - clippings, 1941, 1943, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - World War II entertainment photographs, no date, ca. early 1940s (Box 105, Folder 7)
    Appears to be related to wartime entertainment. With images from Watch Your Credit US Army Signal Corp visits/performances.
  - World War II entertainment snapshots, no date (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Series 9. Appearances and Events, no dates, ca. 1940s-1980s; Boxes 28-32, 36, 41, 48-50, 57, 77, 105, 110, 113, 132
  The Appearances and Events series consists of correspondence, clippings, photos, and ephemera related to Bolgers personal appearances at philanthropic, political, and other various small events. Some of the events appear to be for organizations and/or causes in which Bolger was interested. The series is arranged alphabetically by appearance/event name.
  - 153rd Anniversary of the War Department - publicity photographs, 1942 (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - 1964 Republican Campaign (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - 1970 Republican dinner (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - American Cancer Society - An Evening with Ray Bolger, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - An Evening with Ray Bolger - photographs, 1970 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Army Ball (The), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Arthritis Foundation, Kansas City, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Athens and London Hilton openings, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Bing Crosby National Pro-Am Golf Tournament - press releases, letters, and ephemera, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra and Buffalo Symphony Orchestra, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - California Mortgage Bankers Association 17th Annual Convention, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Charities, 1950, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Chicago Armed Forces day - spots, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Community Chest campaign correspondence, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Cypress College Bicentennial Award, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Eisenhower Inauguration (folder 1 of 3), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Signed thank you letters to Bolger from Dwight D. Eisenhower and Richard Nixon.
  - Eisenhower Inauguration (folder 2 of 3), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Eisenhower Inauguration (folder 3 of 3), 1957 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Emerson College Award, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies luncheon, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - First National Bank performance, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - George Abbot dinner, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Good cause appearances and events photographs, 1942, 1960s (Box 105, Folder 8)
    Including National Conference of Christians and Jews, New York World's Fair, National Jewish Hospital at Denver dedication ceremony of Children's Treatment Center, Sports Award luncheon, American Red Cross headquarters visit.
  - Good cause events and appearances, no date, 1957, ca. 1980s (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Good Friday, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Heart Association, 1960s, 1971, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Heart Association, 1964, 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Hilton Tower Honolulu opening, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - IBM 1978 Golden Circle, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - IBM Golden Circle, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - International Ball, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Kansas City Philharmonic, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Kentucky Derby, 1958 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Kids Are People Too, no date (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Ladies of Charity luncheon, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Lady with the Lamp (The) premiere, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln Day dinner, 1967-1968 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Lotos Club reception - photographs, telegrams, and ephemera, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Marajen Stevick art showing, no date (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Martin Luther Hospital Medical Center Autumn Ambrosia, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Milliken Breakfast Show, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Minneapolis Boys Clubs benefit, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    With Loretta Young and Carol Channing.
  - Motion Picture Home Show in the Louis B. Mayer Theater, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Mountain Valley Water Centennial Show, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews award luncheon, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews Brotherhood Award Dinner, 1972 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - New Orleans Hilton, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - New York Hilton opening ceremonies, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - New York Hilton publicity photographs, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Nixon Republican Campaign letters and papers, 1960, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Oscar Salutes ASCAP dinner, 1984 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Philadelphia Civic Ballet Company En Point Award, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Pictures of a City: A Musical Celebration - program with plaque, no date, 1980 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    Appears to be for IBM Corporate Recognition Event. Includes program treatment.
  - Political advocacy correspondence, ephemera, and clippings, 1960s, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Political advocacy correspondence, ephemera, and clippings, 1956, 1960s - 1970s (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Ray Bolger Overture - script, no date (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Republican National Committee remarks (not written for Bolger), no date (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Ripley's Chasen party, 1983 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Russian War Relief, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Saint John's Hospital and Health Center Foundation, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Spastic Children's League, 197 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Speech material, no date (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - St. Catherine's Church benefit, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Sugar Ray's Youth Foundation, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Tehran International Film Festival - telegrams, ephemera, clippings, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    Removed from binder for preservation purposes.
  - Texas Film Festival, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Texas Film Society Achievement Award honoring Mervyn Leroy, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    Program, photograph, holographic notes.
  - UNICEF spots, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - United Way End of the Rainbow Victory dinner, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - University of Detroit 4th Annual Awards Dinner, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Valley Music Hall benefit, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Valley Music Hall, Salt Lake City - contracts, 1965-1966 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Western Airlines Alaska Junket, 1967-1968 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - White House News Photographers Association dinner, 1955, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Wolf Trap Birthday Benefit, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - World Mercy Fund, 1973, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Series 10. Unidentified Projects, no dates, ca. 1930s-1980s; Boxes 1, 16-28, 31, 33, 37, 50, 54, 57, 74, 76, 79-80, 110
  The bulk of the Unidentified Projects series are scripts which are not identified with known projects, and which may have been submitted to Bolger for his consideration, and which may or may not have been produced. Additionally there is a small amount of writings that appear to be sketches, bits, ideas, lyrics, synopses, treatments, and titled and untitled stories. Also included is a small number of files collated by the processor containing holographic notes which may have been written by Ray and/or Gwen Bolger. There is no specific arrangement to the series.
  - $25,000 Reward! - pitch, no date (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 27 Hawthorne Road - scripts, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Affair (The) - synopsis and script, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Alexander - script, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - All the Ships at Sea by William J. Lederer (copy of book), no date (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Angel Hair - script, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Articles and Talks by Others, no date (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - At Home Abroad - outline, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - At the Shores - script, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Berle-Bolger-Raye - spot scripts, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Blueprints for proposed apartment building, no date (Box 122)
  - Buck-Tens solicitation (form letter from Bolger), 1972 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Cad (The) - script, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Calling (A) - script, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    See also Widgin.
  - Cinders manuscript, no date (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Command Performance - routine, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Country Cousin - outline and pilot script, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Curtain Never Falls (The) - script, no date (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Dance Players Studio itinerary, lyrics, and stage plan, no date (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Dance Rex - script, no date (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Dance with the King - outline, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Day of the Locust (The) - script, no date (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Deceit by Robert Spalding Coleman, no date (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Don Quixote ballet libretto, 1950 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Donald Quixote - treatment, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Doraleen and Fuzzy Vague - script, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Dream Boat - script and correspondence, 1951, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Fenwick - script, no date (Box 24, Folder 1)
    With published story book.
  - Fenwick - second draft script, no date (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Fenwick - storyline treatment and character artwork, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Finian's Rainbow - scripts, 1947, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Flying High - script, no date (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Episode title: The Challenges.
  - Footsteps - script, no date (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Ford Dealers' Show - script and music, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Genius (The) - script, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - George - treatment, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Gibbsville - final draft script, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Episode title: How Old, How Young.
  - Gift Horse (The) - script, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Going Strong - script, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Golden Days - script, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Handwritten jokes, lyrics, etc., no date (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Having Babies - script, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Episode title: Captive.
  - Here We Are - script, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Hill Beyond a Hill (A) - script, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Holograph notes and typescript pages, no date (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Appears to be unrelated projects.
  - Holograph notes, typescript pages, and itinerary, no date (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - How to Make a Man - script, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Jokes and lyrics, no date (Box 79, Folder 5)
    With holographic lyrics for I Love to Eat.
  - Jonas - script, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Kilgallen piece, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Land of Laughs (The) - script, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lecture material, valedictorian address, and Generation Gap pamphlet, no date, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Leroy - pitches, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    With variations on pitches.
  - Leroy - pitches, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Leroy - pitches, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Leroy - possible treatment, no date (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Leroy - script and treatment duplicates, 1960 (Box 128)
  - Leroy - script and treatments, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    With Where's Ray? treatments.
  - Leroy - treatment for stage, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Let's Face It - manuscript, no date (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Lifemoves - proposal, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Likely Story (A) - script, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Little Dog Laughed (The) - script, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Little Me - final script, no date (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Long John Silver - script, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Look Homeward Angel - script, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Lovebirds (The) - revised draft script, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Main Street to Broadway - script, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Man in the Santa Claus Suit - final draft script, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)